

#### **WEB**

- https://emanuel-rieiro.github.io/cv/

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a data scientist currently finishing my master thesis with over 5 years of experience in development and analysis.

I consider myself to be a very proactive and energetic person with an addiction for structural order, as a developer I let that reflect on my work on a daily basis, being very diligent in writing tests and documentation.

I always wanted to be an engineer, but fate brought me to have a background in finance. For 2023 I plan to start a college degree in software engineering as I finish my masters in data science.

# CONTACT

FMAII:

emanuel-0@hotmail.com

CELLPHONE: 598 92 23 30 94

#### **HOBBIES**

- -Programming
- -Mate
- -Exercise

# EMANUEL RIEIRO

# Data Scientist

## **EDUCATION**

Universidad Tecnológica del Uruguay (UTEC)

2021 - Present

Msc. Data Science. Currently finishing my thesis.

Universidad de la República (UDELAR)

2014 - 2020

**Accountant**. Although I consider myself a tech person from heart, I have more of a financial background.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Tata SA – Data Scientist

27/09/2021 - Present

Data Science developer for the fidelity program of the biggest retail chain in Uruguay. Worked in customer behavior analytics, process automation and modeling.

### El Dorado - Business Intelligence Developer

01/03/2020 - 17/09/2021

Upgrade from the Data Analyst role, since I was already doing automation and working with the data base, I was offered to switch positions, although I kept doing a lot of data analyst work.

### El Dorado – Data Analyst

10/12/2018 - 01/03/2020

Tasks: Help with the definition and analytics surrounding KPI, creating and automating dashboards. Market Research in search for opportunities in products or prices.

# **SKILLS**

